headlinesnetwork.com 2017-08-10

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy – YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS**

**Effective Date: November 2016 (Last updated: February 2017)**

**This Privacy Policy applies to our web and mobile services where it appears.**

This Privacy Policy describes how we collect, use and disclose information that we collect about users through the web and mobile services where it appears (collectively, the “Services”).

**We collect information about you.**

**Automated information.   **We collect personal information about users over time and across different websites when you use the Services.  We also have third party vendors that collect information this way.  We collect statistical information about how users use the Services.  Using technologies such as cookies, web beacons and similar technologies, we may automatically collect information about your computer, mobile devices, and online activity when you access the Services, including information about your browsing history. If you use our Services, we may collect information about the browser you’re using. We might look at what site you came from, or what site you visit when you leave us.  Learn more about these tools and how you can control them, _[here](http://headlinesnetwork.com/ads)_ (or by visiting _<http://headlinesnetwork.com/ads>_ ).

**Information from other sources.**   We may combine the information that we collect with information that we obtain from other sources, such as third party service providers.  We may combine information we get from you with information about you we get from third parties.

**How we use your information.**

**We use information to improve our products and services.** We might use your information to customize your experience with us.  We may use your information for research on our users’ demographics, interests, and behavior to help us operate the Services or for other business purposes.  We may use your information to serve you with advertising content in which we think you’ll be interested.    

**We use information to look at site trends and customer interests.** We may use your information to make our website and products better. We may use your information to customize your experience with us.

**We use information for security purposes.** We may use information to protect our company, our customers, or our Services.

**We use information for marketing purposes.** For example, we might send you information about special promotions or offers. We might tell you about new features or products. These might be our own offers or products, or third party offers or products we think you might find interesting.

**We use information as otherwise permitted by law or as we may notify you.** For example, we may use your IP address for identification purposes in cooperation with internet service providers or law enforcement agencies.

**We may share information with third parties.**

**We will share information with our corporate affiliates.   **

**We will share information with third parties who perform services on our behalf.  **We may share your information with authorized service providers that help us provide the Services or perform other business functions for us. 

**We will share information with our business partners.** For example, we will share information with third party media companies and publishers we partner with to provide the Services. These partners may use your information for their marketing purposes. For example, these partners may serve you with advertising content based on your interests. 

**We will share information if we think we have to in order to comply with the law or to protect ourselves.** For example, we will share information at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, or to verify or enforce compliance with our internal policies and applicable laws. We will share information to respond to a court order or subpoena. Or, we might share information when we are investigating potential fraud. We may share your information whenever we believe disclosure is necessary to limit our liability or to protect or enforce the rights, interests or safety of our products and services, our users or others.

**We may share information with any successor to all or part of our business.** For example, if part of our business is sold we may give our customer list as part of that transaction.

**We may share information in an aggregated or other non-personally identifiable form.**

**We may share information as otherwise described to you at the point of collection.**

**You have certain choices about how we use your information.**

**You can control cookies and tracking tools.** To learn how to manage how we – and our vendors – use cookies and other tracking tools, and to read our **Do Not Track** policy, please click _[here](http://headlinesnetwork.com/ads)_ (or visit _<http://headlinesnetwork.com/ads>_ ).

**The Services are not intended for children**.

Our Services are meant for adults. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13 without permission from a parent or guardian. If you are a parent or legal guardian and think your child under 13 has given us information, you can email us at privacy@headlinesnetwork.com. You can also write to us at the address listed at the end of this Policy. Please mark your inquiries “COPPA Information Request.” Parents, you can learn more about how to protect children's privacy on-line _[here](https://www.consumer.ftc.gov/articles/0031-protecting-your-childs-privacy-online)_ (or visit _<https://www.consumer.ftc.gov/articles/0031-protecting-your-childs-privacy-online>_ ).

**Your California privacy right** s.

Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us one time each year if we have shared personal customer information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes, and providing contact information for such third parties. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to the following address: 350 N. Orleans Street, 10-S Chicago, IL 60654. Indicate in your letter that you are a California resident making a “Shine the Light” inquiry.

**We use standard security measures.**

The Internet is not 100% secure. We cannot promise that your use of our Services will be completely safe. We encourage you to use caution when using the Internet.

**We may link to other sites or have third party services on our site we don’t control.**

If you click on a third party link, you will be taken to websites or platforms we do not control. This includes sites that may include our logo because we partner with that company. This Policy does not apply to the privacy practices of that website. That website sets its own cookies, collects data and/or has its own privacy practices. Read the privacy policy of other websites carefully. We are not responsible for these third party sites. Our Services may also serve third party ads or content that contains the third party’s own cookies or tracking technologies. To learn more, click _[here](http://headlinesnetwork.com/ads)_ (or visit _<http://headlinesnetwork.com/ads>_ ). We do not control the use of those technologies.

**Feel free to contact us if you have more questions.**

If you have any questions about this Policy or other privacy concerns, please email us at privacy@headlinesnetwork.com. You can also write to us at:

Aggrego Services, LLC   
350 N. Orleans Street,   
10-S Chicago, IL 60654   
Attention: Privacy Questions

**We may update this Policy.**

From time to time we may change our privacy policies. We will notify you of any material changes to our Policy as required by law. We will also post an updated copy on the Services. Please check the Services periodically for updates.

© 2017 Aggrego Services, LLC. All rights reserved.
